Guide to the Abe Burrows collection of sound recordings [sound recording]
The New York Public Library. Rodgers and Hammerstein Archives of Recorded Sound.
Abe Burrows collection of sound recordings [sound recording]
*L (Special) 99-12
20488
Papers, documents, and photographs can be found as part of the Abe Burrows Papers, *T-Mss 2000-006, in the Billy Rose Theatre Division
Burrows, Abe, 1910-1985
The New York Public Library. Rodgers and Hammerstein Archives of Recorded Sound. New York Public Library for the Performing Arts, Dorothy and Lewis B. Cullman Center 40 Lincoln Center Plaza, New York, NY 10023-7498
sound recordings
This collection contains recordings of the complete runs of both "The Abe Burrows Show" and "Breakfast with Burrows." There are also recordings of many of the numerous guest appearances Burrows made on other radio and television programs such as "The Bing Crosby Show" and shows for which he was a writer, such as "The Philip Morris Holiday Show." In addition, there are home and private recordings of the Burrows family and 3 unproduced musicals: "Jacobowsky," "Tango Mogador" and "Poilu.".
Abe Burrows (1910-1985) was a playwright, director and radio personality. Born in New York City, he began in radio as a writer for shows such as Texaco Star Theatre, Duffy's Tavern, and the Joan Davis Show. He hosted two of his own radio shows, The Abe Burrows Show (CBS, 1946-47) and Breakfast with Burrows (CBS, 1949). He often appeared as a guest on television shows such as PM East and the Dinah Shore Show.
Burrows started his entertainment career by performing satirical songs at Hollywood parties. These songs became the basis for his radio shows, where he would perform them along with witty commentary about the issues of the day. After radio, he became a prominent Broadway director. He also wrote the books for many successful shows, including Guys and Dolls and How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying.
The sound recordings in this collection were separated from the Billy Rose Theatre Division.
This collection contains recordings of the complete runs of both The Abe Burrows Show and Breakfast with Burrows. There are also recordings of many of the numerous guest appearances Burrows made on other radio and television programs such as the Bing Crosby Show and shows for which he was writer, such as the Philip Morris Holiday Show. In addition, there are home and private recordings of the Burrows family and 2 unproduced musicals: Jacobowsky, Tango Mogador and Poilu.
The collection is divided into 7 series:
I. The Abe Burrows Show
II. Breakfast with Burrows
III. Other radio shows
IV. Television programs
V. Other Burrows material
VI. Musicals
VII. Miscellaneous
Abe Burrows Estate
Papers, documents and photographs relating to Abe Burrows can be found in the Abe Burrows Collection, *T-MSS 2000-066, The Billy Rose Theatre Division.
Access to original items by permission only. Some items may be available as service copies. Other items which need preservation work may require advance notification for use. Refer to item descriptions in individual catalog records for more information.
Users never directly handle sound recordings. Listening selections are transmitted through a playback system.
Some items have been transferred to preservation and service copies. Original items which have not been transferred may require advance notification for use. Refer to item description for more information.
Burrows, Abe, 1910-1985; Crosby, Bing, 1903-1977; Radio programs; Television talk shows; Abe Burrows show (Radio program); Bing Crosby show (Radio program); Breakfast with Burrows (Radio program)
- Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., 1947-48; 915892
  The complete run of Abe Burrows' first radio show in which he was host.
  The shows are arranged chronologically.
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., July 9, 1947; *LTC 9189; 915893; "Audition - not broadcast." "Old man river" arranged by DeLugg. Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5550, *LJ-12 5551, *LJ-12 5677, *LJ-12 5678.; Contents: Tokyo Rose / Abe Burrows -- Girl with the three blue eyes / Abe Burrows -- Show boat. Ol' man river / Jerome Kern -- Waukeshaw natural bridge / Abe Burrows.; 4 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Kern, Jerome, 1885-1945; Milton DeLugg Quartet; Tokyo Rose; Girl with the three blue eyes; Show boat. Ol' man river; Waukeshaw Natural Bridge
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., July 26, 1947; *LTC 9181; 915894; "Ol' man river" arranged by Milton DeLugg for the Quartet. Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5602, *LJ-12 5603.; Contents: Tokyo Rose / Abe Burrows -- Girl with the three blue eyes / Abe Burrows -- Showboat. Ol' man river; arr / Jerome Kern -- Waukeshaw natural bridge / Abe Burrows.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Kern, Jerome; Milton DeLugg Quartet; Tokyo Rose; Girl with the three blue eyes; Showboat. Ol' man river; arr; Waukeshaw Natural Bridge
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., August 2, 1947; *LTC 9181; 915895; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "Minute Waltz" arranged by DeLugg for the Quartet. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5604, *LJ-12 5605.; Contents: Hello type song / Abe Burrows -- Rock and the rose / Abe Burrows -- Waltzes, piano, op. 64. No. 1; arr / Frederic Chopin -- Boulder Dam / Abe Burrows.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Chopin, Frédéric, 1810-1849; Milton DeLugg Quartet; Hello type song; Rock and The Rose; Waltzes, piano, op. 64. No. 1; arr; Boulder Dam
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., August 9, 1947; *LTC 9181; 915896; "Flight of the bumblebee" arranged by DeLugg for the Quartet. Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5606, *LJ-12 5607, *LJ-12 5680, *LJ-12 5681.; Contents: I'm not sick of you / Abe Burrows -- Heinz the huntsman / Abe Burrows -- Skazka o tsare Saltane. Nu, teper, moi shmel; arr / Nikolay Rimsky-Korsakov -- Pansy in my garden / Abe Burrows.; 4 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Rimsky-Korsakov, Nikolay, 1844-1908; Milton DeLugg Quartet; I'm not sick of you; Heinz the Huntsman; Skazka o tsare Saltane. Nu, teper, moi shmel; arr; Pansy In My Garden
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., August 16, 1947; *LTC 9181; 915897; Robert Maxwell, harp; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5608, *LJ-12 5609.; Contents: You're playing ping-pong with my heart / Abe Burrows -- I'm goin' back east to the west / Abe Burrows -- Medley: It ain't neccesarily so; I got rhythm / George Gershwin -- Herman the harp / Abe Burrows.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; Maxwell, Robert, 1921-; DeLugg, Milton; Gershwin, George, 1898-1937; Milton DeLugg Quartet; You're playing ping-pong with my heart; I'm goin' back east to the west; Medley: It ain't neccesarily so; I got rhythm; Herman the harp
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., August 23, 1947; *LTC 9181; 915898; Guest: Frank Loesser. Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5610, *LJ-12 5611.; Contents: You ate up a hunk of my heart / Abe Burrows -- Bloop bleep / Frank Loesser -- Tallahasse / Frank Loesser.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Loesser, Frank, 1910-1969; Milton DeLugg Quartet; You ate up a hunk of my heart; Bloop bleep; Tallahasse
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., August 30, 1947; *LTC 9181; 915899; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. Includes a "Friendly Philosopher" skit. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5612, *LJ-12 5613.; Contents: Stationary type song / Abe Burrows -- Ron, ron, ron / Abe Burrows -- Zone 28 / Milton DeLugg.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Milton DeLugg Quartet; Stationary type song; Ron, ron, ron; Zone 28
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., September 6, 1947; *LTC 9182; 915900; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "Hora staccato" arranged by DeLugg for the Quartet. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5638, *LJ-12 5639.; Contents: I didn't mean it when I slugged you / Abe Burrows -- Bela Lugosi / Abe Burrows -- Hora staccato; arr / Grigoras Dinicu -- Sea chanty / Abe Burrows.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Dinicu, Grigoras; Milton DeLugg Quartet; I didn't mean it when I slugged you; Bela Lugosi; Hora staccato; arr; Sea Chanty
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., September 13, 1947; *LTC 9182; 915901; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "Stompin' at the Savoy" arranged by DeLugg for the Quartet. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5544, *LJ-12 5545, *LJ-12 5640, *LJ-12 5641.; Contents: My girl is crazy 'bout me / Abe Burrows -- What do you got? / Abe Burrows -- Stompin' at the Savoy; arr / Chick Webb -- Los Angeles / Abe Burrows.; 4 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Webb, Chick; Milton DeLugg Quartet; My girl is crazy 'bout me; What do you got?; Stompin' at the Savoy; arr; Los Angeles
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., September 20, 1947; *LTC 9182; 915902; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "Whistler and his dog" arranged by DeLugg for the Quartet. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5642, *LJ-12 5643.; Contents: Smile / Abe Burrows -- John C. Shulzenhammer High / Abe Burrows -- Whistler and his dog / Arthur Pryor -- Upper Peabody / Abe Burrows.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Pryor, Arthur, 1870-1942; Milton DeLugg Quartet; Smile; John C. Shulzenhammer High; Whistler and his dog; Upper Peabody
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., September 27, 1947; *LTC 9182; 915903; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "I wonder who's kissing her now" arranged by DeLugg for the Quartet. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5644, *LJ-12 5645.; Contents: Leave us, face it / Frank Loesser -- Columbus Day / Abe Burrows -- I wonder who's kissing her now -- No matter / Abe Burrows.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Loesser, Frank, 1910-1969; Milton DeLugg Quartet; Leave us, face it; Columbus Day; No matter; I Wonder Who's Kissing Her Now
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., October 4, 1947; *LTC 9182; 915904; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "Peg o' my heart" arranged by DeLugg for the Quartet. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5646, *LJ-12 5647.; Contents: Why does everybody call me Louis / Eddie Maxwell -- You can't keep breaking my heart / Abe Burrows -- Peg o' my heart -- That train's goin' south / Abe Burrows.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Maxwell, Eddie; Milton DeLugg Quartet; Why does everybody call me Louis; You Can't Keep Breaking My Heart; That train's goin' south; Peg O' My Heart
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., October 11, 1947; *LTC 9182; 915905; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "Jealousy" arranged by DeLugg for the Quartet. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5648, *LJ-12 5649.; Contents: Rain / Abe Burrows -- Hula maiden / Abe Burrows -- Jealousy.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Milton DeLugg Quartet; Rain; Hula maiden; Jealousy
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., October 18, 1947; *LTC 9183; 915906; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "Tiko-tiko" arranged by DeLugg for the Quartet. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5650, *LJ-12 5651.; Contents: Midnight poker game / Abe Burrows -- Open road / Abe Burrows -- Tiko-tiko.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Milton DeLugg Quartet; Midnight poker game; Open Road; Tiko-tiko
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., October 21, 1947; *LTC 9198; 915907; Performers: Abe Burrows, Margaret Whiting, singers; Milton DeLugg and his quartet and orchestra; Larry Adler, harmonica; Bob LeMond, announcer. "Audition" -- On container. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LT-10 9779.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; Whiting, Margaret; DeLugg, Milton; Adler, Larry; LeMond, Bob; Milton DeLugg Quartet
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., October 25, 1947; *LTC 9183; 915908; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "I wonder who's kissing her now" arranged by DeLugg for the Quartet. Includes a "Friendly Philosopher" skit. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5652, *LJ-12 5653.; Contents: Who? / Abe Burrows -- Heinz the huntsman / Abe Burrows -- I wonder who's kissing her now.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Milton DeLugg Quartet; Who?; Heinz the Huntsman; I Wonder Who's Kissing Her Now
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., November 1, 1947; *LTC 9183; 915909; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "Caravan" arranged by DeLugg for the Quartet. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5654, *LJ-12 5655.; Contents: Give me a kiss / Abe Burrows -- Effie / Abe Burrows -- Caravan -- Western type song / Abe Burrows.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Milton DeLugg Quartet; Give me a kiss; Effie; Western type song; Caravan
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., November 8, 1947; *LTC 9183; 915910; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "In a little Spanish town" arranged by DeLugg for the Quartet. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5656, *LJ-12 5657.; Contents: Girl with the three blue eyes / Abe Burrows -- Everything I've got belongs to you -- In a little spanish town -- Keep singing / Abe Burrows.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Milton DeLugg Quartet; Girl with the three blue eyes; Keep Singing; Everything I've got belongs to you; In a Little Spanish Town
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., November 15, 1947; *LTC 9183; 915911; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "Near you" arranged by DeLugg for the Quartet. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5658, *LJ-12 5659.; Contents: Tokyo Rose / Abe Burrows -- Gypsy's violin / Abe Burrows -- Near you -- Tannenbaum / Harry Ruby.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Ruby, Harry; Milton DeLugg Quartet; Tokyo Rose; Gypsy's Violin; Tannenbaum; Near you
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., November 22, 1947; *LTC 9183; 915912; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "Chapeneques" arranged by DeLugg for the Quartet. Includes a "Friendly Philosopher" skit. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5660, *LJ-12 5661.; Contents: Why should I laugh / Abe Burrows -- Rock and the rose / Abe Burrows -- Chapeneques.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Milton DeLugg Quartet; Why should I laugh; Rock and The Rose; Chapeneques
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., November 29, 1947; *LTC 9184; 915913; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "The man I love" arranged by DeLugg for the Quartet. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5672, *LJ-12 5673.; Contents: Little Dutch song / Abe Burrows -- Act, little movie star, act / Abe Burrows -- The man I love / George Gershwin.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Gershwin, George; Milton DeLugg Quartet; Little Dutch song; Act, little movie star, act; The Man I Love
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., December 6, 1947; *LTC 9184; 915914; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "Minute waltz" arranged by DeLugg for the Quartet. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5670, *LJ-12 5671.; Contents: After / Abe Burrows -- Mexican song / Abe Burrows -- Waltzes, piano, op. 64. No. 1; arr / Frederic Chopin.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Chopin, Frédéric, 1810-1849; Milton DeLugg Quartet; After; Mexican song; Waltzes, piano, op. 64. No. 1; arr
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., December 13, 1947; *LTC 9184; 915915; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "Pass the peace pipe" arranged by DeLugg for the Quartet. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5668, *LJ-12 5669.; Contents: This must be love / Abe Burrows -- Pass the peace pipe / Hugh Martin -- Low down blues / Abe Burrows.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Martin, Hugh, 1914-; Milton DeLugg Quartet; This Must Be Love; Pass the Peace Pipe; Low down blues
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., December 20, 1947; *LTC 9184; 915916; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. Christmas carols arranged by DeLugg for the Quartet. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-10 1776, *LJ-12 5666, *LJ-12 5667.; Contents: Sweet memories / Abe Burrows -- Christmas medley: O little town of Bethlehem; Deck the halls -- Smile / Abe Burrows.; 3 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Milton DeLugg Quartet; Sweet Memories; Smile; Christmas medley: O little town of Bethlehem; Deck the halls
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., December 27, 1947; *LTC 9184; 915917; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "Jingle bells" arranged by DeLugg for the Quartet. Includes a "Friendly Philosopher" skit. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5664, *LJ-12 5665.; Contents: Let's say we're sorry / Abe Burrows -- Jingle bells -- If / Abe Burrows.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Milton DeLugg Quartet; Let's Say We're Sorry; If; Jingle Bells
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., January 3, 1948; *LTC 9184; *LTC 9198; 915918; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. Preservation copy in: *LT-10 9779. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5662, *LJ-12 5663.; Contents: It's getting late / Abe Burrows -- Sea chanty / Abe Burrows.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Milton DeLugg Quartet; It's getting late; Sea Chanty
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., January 10, 1948; *LTC 9185; 915919; Broadcast from New York City. Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "Bim Bam Boom" arranged by DeLugg. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5555, *LJ-12 5560, *LJ-12 5561, *LJ-12 5562, *LJ-12 5614, *LJ-12 5615.; Contents: You're playing ping-pong with my heart / Abe Burrows -- Bim bam boom -- Duke of Dittendorten / Abe Burrows.; 6 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Milton DeLugg Quartet; You're playing ping-pong with my heart; Duke of Dittendorten; Bim bam boom
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., January 17, 1948; *LTC 9185; 915920; Broadcast from Philadelphia. Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "Take me out to the ball game" arranged by DeLugg. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5616, *LJ-12 5617, *LJ-12 5682, *LJ-12 5683.; Contents: Ron, ron, ron / Abe Burrows -- Take me out to the ball game -- Waukeshaw natural bridge / Abe Burrows.; 4 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Milton DeLugg Quartet; Ron, ron, ron; Waukeshaw Natural Bridge; Take me out to the Ball Game
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., January 24, 1948; *LTC 9185; 915921; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "Four leaf clover" arranged by DeLugg. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5618, *LJ-12 5619.; Contents: You taught me / Abe Burrows -- Four leaf clover -- I'm goin' back east to the west / Abe Burrows.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Milton DeLugg Quartet; You Taught Me; I'm goin' back east to the west; Four leaf clover
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., January 31, 1948; *LTC 9185; 915922; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "Papa won't you dance with me" arranged by DeLugg. Includes spoofs of commercial jingles. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5620, *LJ-12 5621.; Contents: If I can only get away from you / Abe Burrows -- Papa, won't you dance with me? / Jule Styne.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Styne, Jule; Milton DeLugg Quartet; If I can only get away from you; Papa, Won't You Dance with Me?
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., February 7, 1948; *LTC 9185; 915923; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "My blue heaven" arranged by DeLugg. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5622, *LJ-12 5623.; Contents: Stationary type song / Abe Burrows -- My blue heaven -- I'll cherish thee / Abe Burrows.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Milton DeLugg Quartet; Stationary type song; I'll Cherish Thee; My Blue Heaven
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., February 14, 1948; *LTC 9185; 915924; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "Best things in life are free" arranged by DeLugg. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5624, *LJ-12 5625.; Contents: What will I say / Abe Burrows -- Good news. Best things in life are free / Ray Henderson -- Low down blues / Abe Burrows.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Henderson, Ray; Milton DeLugg Quartet; What will I say; Good news. Best things in life are free; Low down blues
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., February 21, 1948; *LTC 9186; 915925; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "Camptown races" arranged by DeLugg for the Quartet. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5626, *LJ-12 5627.; Contents: George Washington / Abe Burrows -- Why can't you find a job / Abe Burrows -- Camptown races / Stephen Collins Foster.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Foster, Stephen Collins, 1826-1864; Milton DeLugg Quartet; George Washington; Why can't you find a job; Camptown Races